Finding Aid for wilsondoncollectiontwo
Clarke Historical Library
- Don Wilson Collection.
  - (Slide Box 4): C.M. slides (3 small slide boxes),undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - (Slide Box 4): H. and E.R.R. slides (3 small slide boxes),undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - (Slide Box 4): M.M.R.R. slides (7 small slide boxes),undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - (Slide Box 4): Tuscola and Saginaw Bay slides (7 small slide boxes),undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - (Slide Box 4): W.C.R.R. slides (9 small slide boxes),undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - (Slide Box 5): T.S.B. slides (6 small slide boxes),undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - (Slide Box 5): T.S.B.Y. slides (5 small slide boxes),undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - (Slide Box 5): T.S.B. Branch slides (4 small slide boxes),undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - (Slide Box 5): T.S.B.R.R. (21 small slide boxes),undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Oversized Folder: Ross and White Company Patents, Blueprint (Copies),April 1948, June 1948 (Folder 1)
  - Oversized Folder: Miscellaneous Materials,January 1918, April 1965, September 1985, undated (Folder 2)
  - Oversized Folder: Detroit, Toledo, Ironton Railroad Co., Ann Arbor Railroad Co., System Map,undated (Folder 3)
  - Oversized Folder: Michigan Department of Transportation, Plans of Proposed Railroad Rehabilitation,May 1986 (Folder 4)
  - Oversized Folder: Ann Arbor Railroad, Plan of Proposed Station at Whitmore Lake, MI,June 1913 (Folder 5)
  - Oversized Folder: Blueprints, Refrigerator Cars, Station Plans,February 1921, February 1934 (Folder 6)
  - Oversized Folder: Ann Arbor Railroad and Steamship Lines Newsletter (Copy), Taking Effect January 18, 1914,January 18, 1914 (Folder 7)
  - Oversized Folder: Automatic Signals Blue-Line Prints, Ohio,June 1963 (Folder 8)
  - Oversized Folder: Ann Arbor Railroad, Lever Circuit Controllers, Redrawn Blue-Line Print,August 14, 1973 (Folder 9)
  - Oversized Folder: Styling and Painting Design, Electro-Motive Division (Electrostatic copy of) Sepia Print,February 1964 (Folder 10)
  - Oversized Folder: Ann Arbor Railroad, Toledo, Ohio, Lucas County, Station Maps of Tracks and Structures (Copies),February 1964 (Folder 11)
  - Oversized Folder: Blue-Line Prints (Copies), Miscellaneous,July 1951, March 1963, undated (Folder 12)
  - Oversized Folder: Village of Chesaning, Blue-Line Print, Rowe Engineering,July 1951, March 1963, undated (Folder 13)
  - Oversized Folder: MI Railroad and Property, Blue-Line Prints,1943, 1964, undated (Folder 14)
  - Oversized Folder: Equipment, Station, and Train Car, Blueprints (Some Copies Included, 1 of 2),1913, 1950, undated (Folder 15)
  - Oversized Folder: Equipment, Station, and Train Car, Blueprints (Some Copies Included, 2 of 2),1924, 1950, undated (Folder 16)
  - Oversized Folder: Ann Arbor Railroad Co., Station Map of Tracks and Structures, Blueprints,1928, 1942, 1945 (Folder 17)
  - Oversized Folder: A.A.R.R. Co., Cadillac, MI, Joint Tracks Connecting with A.A.R.R.-P.R.R. Belt Track, Blueprint,February 1927 (Folder 18)
  - Oversized Folder: Blueprints, Detroit, Toledo, Ironton Railroad Co., Ann Arbor Railroad Co.,1964, 1980, undated (Folder 19)
  - Oversized Folder: St. Louis, MI, Property Blueprint,1964, 1980, undated (Folder 20)
  - 2016 Addition: Abandonment Petitions, Ann Arbor Car Ferry Scholes (copies),1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 2016 Addition: Abandonment Petitions, Car Ferry Facts, Proposals (copies),1972-1973, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 2016 Addition: Abandonment Petitions, Correspondence (copies),1972-1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 2016 Addition: Abandonment Petitions, Economics of Railroad Abandonment, by Abandonment Petitions, by James R. Nelson,[after 1972] (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 2016 Addition: Abandonment Petitions, Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC) Docket Exhibits,1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 2016 Addition: Abandonment Petitions, Meeting Minutes and Reports of Meetings (copies),1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 2016 Addition: Abandonment Petitions, Michigan Public Service Commission (MPSC) relocation of grade crossing of Ann Arbor Railroad (A2R2), Wexford County (copy),1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 2016 Addition: Abandonment Petitions, Nine Month Progress Report on A2R2 System by V. M. Malanaphy (copy),July 1978] (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 2016 Addition: Abandonment Petitions, Statement of C.E. Nelson, Appendices A-F (copy),[1972] (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 2016 Addition: Abandonment Petitions, Abandonment Petitions, Track and Signal Layout, Alexis to Galena Street, Toledo, Ohio (copy),1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 2016 Addition: Accident Reports, 1929, 1961 (scattered); Dundee to Owosso Track Conditions Inspection Report (copy),1975 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 2016 Addition: Ann Arbor Railroad and related, Bulletins, Circulars Orders, Time Schedules (some copies),1907-1972 (scattered) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Oversized Folder: Ross and White Company Patents, Blueprint (Copies),April 1948, June 1948 (Folder 21)
  - 2016 Addition: Clippings (copies), Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1965-1997, undated; and 3 photographs, 1974,1965-1997, undated; 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 2016 Addition: Clippings Scanned (copies),1970-1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 2016 Addition: Clippings Scanned (copies),1980-1985, 1988, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 2016 Addition: Diesel Locomotive Engine Schematics (copies),1955, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 2016 Addition: DVD of Scanned Collection Contents,2015 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 2016 Addition: Federal Maritime Financial Regulations (copies),1971 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 2016 Addition: Gerritsen, Arndt, A2R2 negatives, positive prints #4,May 16, 2015 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 2016 Addition: Gerritsen, Arndt, A2R2 negatives, positive prints #1,May 17, 2015 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 2016 Addition: Historic Photographs, negatives, positive prints, May 2015 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 2016 Addition: Locomotive Inspection and Repair Records, 1972-1973; and Reports, 1969-1972 (Scattered),1972-1973; 1969-1972 (Scattered) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Changeover Ceremony, negatives, positive prints,May 2015 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Ann Arbor Railroad System and related railways Income Statements (copies),1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Ann Arbor Railroad System News Releases (copies),1978-1985 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Carload Volumes Per Station (copies),1976-1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Conrail- Ann Arbor Division Maintenance Program and Track Chart (copy),1977 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Correspondence (copies),1979, 1981-1982, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Dun and Bradstreet Report,1981 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Lake Michigan Rail Freight Study Report for Michigan Dept. of Transportation by Transportation and Distribution Associates, Inc. (copy),1983 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, List of Industries on the Ann Arbor by Station, Circular,1967 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Railway Company Position Paper on Integrated Tug-Barge Proposal (copy),1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Michigan Northern Railway Company Income Statement (copy),1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Michigan State Transportation Committee Minutes (copies),February 1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Norfolk and Western Railway Company Operations Bulletin (copy),1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Northwest Rail Study (copy),1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Sand Tariff 1739-A (copy),1972 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Toledo, Ohio, Site Plan, Ottowa Yard (copy),1978 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, Tuscola and Saginaw Bay Railway Five Year Plan (copy),1981 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, U.S. Bankruptcy Court Hearing Notice (copy),1983 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - 2016 Addition: Michigan Interstate Era, V. M. Malanaphy Grant Application (copy),1981 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson negatives, positive prints #1,May 10, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson negatives, positive prints #1,May 10, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson negatives, positive prints #1,May 10, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson negatives, positive prints #1,May 10, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson negatives, positive prints #1-3,May 12, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson negatives, positive prints #1-3,May 13, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson negatives, positive prints #1,May 14, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson negatives, positive prints #1-7,May 15, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson negatives, positive prints #1-2,May 16, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson negatives, positive prints #2-3,May 17, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson negatives, positive prints #1 each for May 18, 21-22, 2015,May 18, 21-22, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson negatives, positive prints #1-2, May 25, 2015, and #1, May 25, 2015May 25-26, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson St. Charles Turn, 1978, negatives, positive prints,May 2015 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - 2016 Addition: Wilson Transportation Day, Owosso, 1978, negatives, positive prints,May 2015 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Legal-size Folder: Abandonment Petitions, Finance Docket No. 263373, 1972; Ann Arbor Application to Abandon Thompsonville line (copy), 1972; Sale of SS City of Milwaukee, 1979,1972; 1979 (Folder 21)